<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<p:sld xmlns:a="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/main" xmlns:r="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships" xmlns:p="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/presentationml/2006/main"><p:cSld><p:spTree><p:nvGrpSpPr><p:cNvPr id="1" name=""/><p:cNvGrpSpPr/><p:nvPr/></p:nvGrpSpPr><p:grpSpPr><a:xfrm><a:off x="0" y="0"/><a:ext cx="0" cy="0"/><a:chOff x="0" y="0"/><a:chExt cx="0" cy="0"/></a:xfrm></p:grpSpPr><p:sp><p:nvSpPr><p:cNvPr id="9" name="Text Placeholder 8"><a:extLst><a:ext uri="{FF2B5EF4-FFF2-40B4-BE49-F238E27FC236}"><a16:creationId xmlns:a16="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2014/main" id="{9445F9D9-0C13-4EDD-838E-062B771FE3A6}"/></a:ext></a:extLst></p:cNvPr><p:cNvSpPr><a:spLocks noGrp="1"/></p:cNvSpPr><p:nvPr><p:ph type="body" sz="quarter" idx="10"/></p:nvPr></p:nvSpPr><p:spPr/><p:txBody><a:bodyPr/><a:lstStyle/><a:p><a:endParaRPr lang="en-GB"/></a:p></p:txBody></p:sp><p:sp><p:nvSpPr><p:cNvPr id="4" name="Text Placeholder 3"/><p:cNvSpPr><a:spLocks noGrp="1"/></p:cNvSpPr><p:nvPr><p:ph type="body" sz="quarter" idx="11"/></p:nvPr></p:nvSpPr><p:spPr/><p:txBody><a:bodyPr/><a:lstStyle/><a:p><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-GB" b="1" dirty="0"/><a:t>As climate change intensifies, brands are helping consumers adapt to new realities brought about by a changing environment.</a:t></a:r></a:p><a:p><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-GB" b="1" dirty="0"/><a:t>The need to adapt to climate change joins the desire to fight it.</a:t></a:r><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-GB" dirty="0"/><a:t> A changing climate means that intense summer heat, erratic weather conditions and water shortages (as well as damaging water surpluses) have become the norm. The </a:t></a:r><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-GB" b="1" dirty="0"/><a:t>National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA)</a:t></a:r><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-GB" dirty="0"/><a:t> predicts that 2020 will be the hottest year on record. Consumers acutely feel the dangers of an unpredictable environment: in 2020, 32% of global consumers ranked climate change among their top three personal risks over the next five years. The five-country global average (including GB, US, China, Germany and Sweden) rose from 16% in 2016 to 32% in 2020 (source: </a:t></a:r><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-GB" b="1" dirty="0"/><a:t>Foresight Factory</a:t></a:r><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-GB" dirty="0"/><a:t>). In response, expect to see changes in how people manage their lives to safeguard their hobbies, households and personal wellbeing. The </a:t></a:r><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-GB" b="1" dirty="0"/><a:t>International Monetary Fund (IMF)</a:t></a:r><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-GB" dirty="0"/><a:t> has dubbed this the “Adaptive Age”. </a:t></a:r></a:p><a:p><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-GB" b="1" dirty="0"/><a:t>Climate resilience will grow in importance.</a:t></a:r><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-GB" dirty="0"/><a:t> Many consumers are resigned to their new reality: in 2020, 26% of global consumers felt that “it is too late to do anything to counter the effects of climate change” (source: </a:t></a:r><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-GB" b="1" dirty="0"/><a:t>Foresight Factory</a:t></a:r><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-GB" dirty="0"/><a:t>). As such, expect climate resilience to grow in value. This will manifest in many ways. For example, time-shifting could become commonplace, whereby popular leisure activities are undertaken during cooler times of the day, such as midnight gardening and pre-dawn workouts. Meanwhile, homeowners will be encouraged to make homes as durable as possible – flood-proofing and energy-efficient climate control will hold growing appeal. Consumers will also want to safeguard their physical and mental wellbeing, so expect more brands to develop climate-proof skincare and apparel, and to dispense stress remedies and pollution-proof dietary advice. </a:t></a:r></a:p><a:p><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-GB" b="1" dirty="0"/><a:t>Smart adaptation is a growing opportunity for brand differentiation</a:t></a:r><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-GB" dirty="0"/><a:t>. Even as the COVID-19 pandemic temporarily stymies efforts to combat climate change, reducing emissions will remain a priority across all verticals. But increasingly, B2C brands will also signal how they can help customers thrive in a changing climate with smart guidance and innovation. Companies will broadcast their efforts to adapt supply chains, stores and product lines to ensure continuity of service. And new disruptors will focus their entire offerings on their ability to adapt to the new climate reality. </a:t></a:r></a:p></p:txBody></p:sp><p:sp><p:nvSpPr><p:cNvPr id="8" name="Title 7"><a:extLst><a:ext uri="{FF2B5EF4-FFF2-40B4-BE49-F238E27FC236}"><a16:creationId xmlns:a16="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2014/main" id="{F81155E6-8BF1-458B-B680-D4A2EBFAC2B5}"/></a:ext></a:extLst></p:cNvPr><p:cNvSpPr><a:spLocks noGrp="1"/></p:cNvSpPr><p:nvPr><p:ph type="title"/></p:nvPr></p:nvSpPr><p:spPr/><p:txBody><a:bodyPr/><a:lstStyle/><a:p><a:r><a:rPr lang="en-GB" dirty="0"/><a:t>Briefing and Signals</a:t></a:r></a:p></p:txBody></p:sp></p:spTree><p:extLst><p:ext uri="{BB962C8B-B14F-4D97-AF65-F5344CB8AC3E}"><p14:creationId xmlns:p14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/powerpoint/2010/main" val="4279913766"/></p:ext></p:extLst></p:cSld><p:clrMapOvr><a:masterClrMapping/></p:clrMapOvr></p:sld>